<resources>
    <string name="app_name">APLAS Animal Tour</string>
    <string name="transition_name">fade_trans</string>
    <string name="insect_content">
        Insects or Insecta (from Latin insectum) are hexapod
        invertebrates and the largest group within the arthropod
        phylum. Definitions and circumscriptions vary; usually,
        insects comprise a class within the Arthropoda. As used
        here, the term Insecta is synonymous with Ectognatha.
        Insects have a chitinous exoskeleton, a three-part body
        (head, thorax and abdomen), three pairs of jointed legs,
        compound eyes and one pair of antennae. Insects are the
        most diverse group of animals; they include more than a
        million described species and represent more than half
        of all known living organisms. The total number of
        extant species is estimated at between six and ten
        million; potentially over 90% of the animal life forms on
        Earth are insects. Insects may be found in nearly all
        environments, although only a small number of species
        reside in the oceans, which are dominated by another
        arthropod group, crustaceans.
    </string>
    <string name="arachnid_content">
        Arachnida (/əˈræknɪdə/) is a class of joint-legged
        invertebrate animals (arthropods), in the subphylum
        Chelicerata. Arachnida includes orders containing spiders
        (the largest order), scorpions, ticks, mites, harvestmen,
        and solifuges. In 2019, a molecular phylogenetic study
        also placed horseshoe crabs in Arachnida.
        Almost all adult arachnids have eight legs, although the
        front pair of legs in some species has converted to a
        sensory function, while in other species, different
        appendages can grow large enough to take on the
        appearance of extra pairs of legs. The term is derived
        from the Greek word ἀράχνη (aráchnē), from the myth of
        the hubristic human weaver Arachne, who was turned
        into a spider.
    </string>
    <string name="mollusc_content">
        Mollusca is the second-largest phylum of invertebrate
        animals after the Arthropoda. The members are known
        as molluscs or mollusks[a] (/ˈmɒləsk/). Around 85,000
        extant species of molluscs are recognized. The number
        of fossil species is estimated between 60,000 and
        100,000 additional species. The proportion of
        undescribed species is very high. Many taxa remain
        poorly studied.
    </string>
    <string name="crustacean_content">
        Crustaceans (Crustacea /krʌˈsteɪʃə/) form a large, diverse
        arthropod taxon which includes such animals as crabs,
        lobsters, crayfish, shrimps, prawns, krill, woodlice, and
        barnacles. The crustacean group can be treated as a
        subphylum under the clade Mandibulata; because of
        recent molecular studies it is now well accepted that the
        crustacean group is paraphyletic, and comprises all
        animals in the clade Pancrustacea other than hexapods.
        Some crustaceans are more closely related to insects and
        other hexapods than they are to certain other
        crustaceans.
    </string>
    <string name="invert_info">
        Any animal that lacks a vertebral column, or backbone, in
        contrast to the cartilaginous or bony vertebrates. More
        than 90 percent of all living animal species are
        invertebrates.
    </string>
    <string-array name="animal_icon">
        <item>animfishes</item>
        <item>animamphibians</item>
        <item>animreptiles</item>
        <item>animbirds</item>
        <item>animmammals</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="animal_video">
        <item>videofishes</item>
        <item>videoamphibians</item>
        <item>videoreptiles</item>
        <item>videobirds</item>
        <item>videomammals</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="animal_titles">
        <item>Fishes</item>
        <item>Amphibians</item>
        <item>Reptiles</item>
        <item>Birds</item>
        <item>Mammals</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="animal_youtube">
        <item>TJN3gJoZqlY</item>
        <item>XI8GPsf6TAc</item>
        <item>6B0apT6VZKk</item>
        <item>8vL_2rF8JHU</item>
        <item>hGonwMTPV6g</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="animal_info">
        <item>
            A group of cold-blooded vertebrates that breathe with gills rather than lungs, live in water, and generally lay eggs, although some bear their young alive.
        </item>
        <item>
            A group of cold-blooded animals which can live on land or in water and who breathes with gills when young and with lungs as an adult.
        </item>
        <item>
            A group of cold-blooded animals which have skins covered with small hard plates called scales and lay eggs.
        </item>
        <item>
            A group of warm-blooded vertebrates distinguished by their feathers and their two legs and two wings.
        </item>
        <item>
            A group of warm-blooded animals that is distinguished by the possession of hair or fur, females that secrete milk for the nourishment of the young, and (typically) the birth of live young.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="mainTitle">Animal Tour</string>
    <string name="prevButton">Prev</string>
    <string name="nextButton">Next</string>
    <string name="title2">World</string>
</resources>